# **ARTYOM ZAGOSKIN**

# iOS Developer

in https://linkedin.com/in/artyomzagoskin

https://github.com/Inxel

artyzago@gmail.com

Open-minded, flexible, mindfulness, collaborative iOS developer with 4+ years of experience. Participate in all phases of development: system design, UI and UX discussion, decomposition and development. Spending spare time exploring new technologies to use it in pet and work projects. Fascinated about my job.

# **LANGUAGES**

### **English**

Professional Working Proficiency

#### Russian

Native

### **CERTIFICATES**

### iOS Development

Napoleon IT Course 2019

#### FCE (CEFR Level - B2)

Cambridge University Press 2019

# SKILLS

- Swift
- SwiftUI
- · Multi-threading
- · Object-Oriented Programming
- Protocol-Oriented Programming
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Time management
- · Agile and Scrum workflow
- JIRA / Confluence / Git

# **EDUCATION**

### **Computer and Information Sciences**

2017 - 2021

South Ural State University

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### iOS Engineer

2021 - present

### <u>Aviasales</u>

The leading travel metasearch company in Eastern Europe and Central Asia (with more then 15 mln unique users monthly).

- Brand-new hotel page and hotels search (75% more bookings)
- Results page (became 1.5x faster) and ticket screen
- Feature management
- SwiftUI (previously UIKit without storyboards)
- · Objective-C to Swift refactoring
- Work in team of 4 iOS developers
- MVVM architecture
- Code review
- UI-, Unit- and snapshot tests
- Interviewer

# iOS Engineer

2019 - 2021

### Napoleon IT

- 1. Retail app:
- Clean Swift (VIP) architecture
- Worked in team of 2 iOS developers
- Developed catalog, authorization, shop cart, etc.
- 2. Platform for local services and specialized jobs:
  - VIPER architecture
  - Developed task creating constructor, transactions history, etc.
- Localization
- Only one iOS developer
- 3. Initialization of app (MVVM + Coordinators).
- 4. Mentor.
- 5. Napoleon IT iOS course lecturer.